### Contact

sean\_gyuris@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sean-gyuris-72b5a1127 (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills

Stratigraphy
Petrology
Organic Geochemistry

Certifications

Portable XRF license

# Sean Gyuris

**Exploration Geologist** 

Greater Sydney Area

# Summary

Early career geologist with a background in sedimentology and low temp geochemistry. Previous exploration roles at Sandfire Resources (ASX:SFR) focused on porphyry associated IS epithermal Cu-Au in the Macquarie Arc of the LFB, as well as for Manuka Resources (ASX:MKR) in the Cobar Basin (NSW) across a range of unique epigenetic sediment-hosted mineral systems.

I have professional experience with most industry standard GIS software packages and a solid grasp on GIS database management.

Alongside this is a growing competency in fullstack Web development with React (NextJS)/Node, Python and open source web mapping (openlayer/postgis/geoserver).

# Experience

Munro Geological Services
Exploration Geologist
May 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months)
Cobar, New South Wales, Australia

#### Sandfire

Exploration Geologist
January 2022 - August 2022 (8 months)

Contract role exploring intermediate sulphidation epithermal Cu-AU targets in the Macquarie Arc

- -AC rig supervision and logging
- -Diamond rig supervision and logging

Manuka Resources Limited
Graduate Exploration Geologist
May 2021 - December 2021 (8 months)

Page 1 of 2

- -RC logging and rig supervision at Wonawinta (Irish style MVT Ag-Zn-Pb)
- -Target generation across several West Cobar basin/Winduck shelf tenements
- -Brownfields exploration at Mt Boppy mine (sediment-hosted hydrothermal Au)

### Geoscience Australia

Geoscience Intern

February 2020 - May 2020 (4 months)

Canberra, Australia

My project involved the compilation of a geological data report of the Petrel sub-basin (Bonaparte) intended to support the 2020 acreage release.

Additional work included the revision of GA's stratigraphic framework for the NW shelf at the P-Tr boundary and contingent reserves research for the Australian Energy Resource Assessment (AERA). This later component of my work has provided me with a high level of competence in the SPE petroleum resource management system (PRMS) classification framework.

# Macquarie University Sedimentology and Stable Isotope Lab Research Assistant

March 2019 - June 2019 (4 months)

IRMS sample preparation, SEM sample preparation (cutting, polishing and ion milling), project logistics, literature review

# Education

## **Charles Sturt University**

Graduate certificate GIS & Remote Sensing · (March 2022 - May 2023)

### Academy of Information Technology

Diploma, Software Development · (July 2022 - January 2023)

### Macquarie University

Master of Science - MSc, Geology / Geochemistry · (2018 - 2020)

#### **UNSW**

Bachelor of Science - BSc, Geography (Earth Science) · (2012 - 2015)

## Marcellin College Randwick

· (2006 - 2011)